[
  {
    "id": "sub-1765291899025",
    "submittedAt": "2025-12-09T14:51:39.025Z",
    "studentId": "user-student-1",
    "quizId": "quiz-1765006830973",
    "courseId": "course-1",
    "earned": 0,
    "possible": 1,
    "responses": [
      {
        "questionId": "qq-1765006830976-3",
        "questionText": "10 + 15",
        "type": "single",
        "selectedIndex": 2,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "correctIndices": [],
        "choices": [
          "25",
          "23",
          "12"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "sub-1765293999466",
    "submittedAt": "2025-12-09T15:26:39.466Z",
    "studentId": "user-student-1",
    "quizId": "quiz-1",
    "courseId": "course-1",
    "earned": 3,
    "possible": 8,
    "responses": [
      {
        "questionId": "q1",
        "questionText": "What is 5 + 7?",
        "type": "single",
        "selectedIndex": 0,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "correctIndex": 2,
        "choices": [
          "10",
          "11",
          "12",
          "13"
        ]
      },
      {
        "questionId": "q2",
        "questionText": "What is 9 + 3?",
        "type": "single",
        "selectedIndex": 1,
        "isCorrect": true,
        "correctIndex": 1,
        "choices": [
          "11",
          "12",
          "13",
          "14"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "sub-1765368316695",
    "submittedAt": "2025-12-10T12:05:16.695Z",
    "studentId": "user-student-1",
    "quizId": "quiz-1765178858235",
    "courseId": "course-1764669321956",
    "earned": 0,
    "possible": 1,
    "responses": [
      {
        "questionId": "qq-1765178858240-5",
        "questionText": "tgyujkl",
        "type": "single",
        "selectedIndex": 1,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "correctIndices": [],
        "choices": [
          "ab",
          "bc",
          "ca"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "sub-1767430097555",
    "submittedAt": "2026-01-03T08:48:17.555Z",
    "studentId": "user-student-1",
    "quizId": "quiz-1765006830973",
    "courseId": "course-1",
    "earned": 0,
    "possible": 2,
    "responses": [
      {
        "questionId": "qq-1765006830976-3",
        "questionText": "10 + 15",
        "type": "single",
        "selectedIndex": 1,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "correctIndices": [],
        "choices": [
          "25",
          "23",
          "12"
        ]
      },
      {
        "questionId": "qq-1765369849506-1",
        "questionText": "testt",
        "type": "single",
        "selectedIndex": null,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "correctIndices": [],
        "choices": [
          "2",
          "3",
          "4"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "sub-1767430125247",
    "submittedAt": "2026-01-03T08:48:45.247Z",
    "studentId": "user-student-1",
    "quizId": "quiz-1765006830973",
    "courseId": "course-1",
    "earned": 0,
    "possible": 2,
    "responses": [
      {
        "questionId": "qq-1765006830976-3",
        "questionText": "10 + 15",
        "type": "single",
        "selectedIndex": 1,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "correctIndices": [],
        "choices": [
          "25",
          "23",
          "12"
        ]
      },
      {
        "questionId": "qq-1765369849506-1",
        "questionText": "testt",
        "type": "single",
        "selectedIndex": null,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "correctIndices": [],
        "choices": [
          "2",
          "3",
          "4"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "sub-1767430142714",
    "submittedAt": "2026-01-03T08:49:02.714Z",
    "studentId": "user-student-1",
    "quizId": "quiz-1765006830973",
    "courseId": "course-1",
    "earned": 0,
    "possible": 2,
    "responses": [
      {
        "questionId": "qq-1765006830976-3",
        "questionText": "10 + 15",
        "type": "single",
        "selectedIndex": 1,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "correctIndices": [],
        "choices": [
          "25",
          "23",
          "12"
        ]
      },
      {
        "questionId": "qq-1765369849506-1",
        "questionText": "testt",
        "type": "single",
        "selectedIndex": null,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "correctIndices": [],
        "choices": [
          "2",
          "3",
          "4"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "sub-1767430641517",
    "submittedAt": "2026-01-03T08:57:21.517Z",
    "studentId": "user-student-1",
    "quizId": "quiz-1765006830973",
    "courseId": "course-1",
    "earned": 1,
    "possible": 2,
    "responses": [
      {
        "questionId": "qq-1765006830976-3",
        "questionText": "10 + 15",
        "type": "single",
        "selectedIndex": 0,
        "isCorrect": true,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "correctIndices": [],
        "choices": [
          "25",
          "23",
          "12"
        ]
      },
      {
        "questionId": "qq-1765369849506-1",
        "questionText": "testt",
        "type": "single",
        "selectedIndex": null,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "correctIndices": [],
        "choices": [
          "2",
          "3",
          "4"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "sub-1767430720911",
    "submittedAt": "2026-01-03T08:58:40.911Z",
    "studentId": "user-student-1",
    "quizId": "quiz-1765006830973",
    "courseId": "course-1",
    "earned": 0,
    "possible": 2,
    "responses": [
      {
        "questionId": "qq-1765006830976-3",
        "questionText": "10 + 15",
        "type": "single",
        "selectedIndex": 1,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "correctIndices": [],
        "choices": [
          "25",
          "23",
          "12"
        ]
      },
      {
        "questionId": "qq-1765369849506-1",
        "questionText": "testt",
        "type": "single",
        "selectedIndex": 1,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "correctIndices": [],
        "choices": [
          "2",
          "3",
          "4"
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]